Dan Feld

Growing Google's Developer Ecosystems

Summary

Results driven technology executive with passion for connecting people & technology. Broad and deep IT Technologies & Cloud Engineering knowledge. Experienced in driving tech and non tech audiences to a successful adoption. Achieved notable success in driving growth and revenues for Cloud and open source platforms, working with Enterprises and Startups.

Experience

Head of Developer Relations Startup & VC Programs, US at Google

January 2015 - Present

Head of Solution Sales - Google Cloud Platform at Google

June 2013 - December 2014 (1 year 6 months)

EIR (Entrepreneur in Residence) at Gemini Israel Ventures

March 2013 - May 2013 (2 months)

VP Sales and Business Development at Newvem

September 2012 - February 2013 (5 months)

Regional Sales Manager EEMEA for Amazon Web Services (AWS), EMEA at Amazon.com

April 2010 - September 2012 (2 years 5 months)

- Head of Sales & Business Development for Amazon's Web Services & Cloud Computing business in Eastern Europe, Middle East, Israel and Africa. Working with customers leveraging from early stage startups to large scale Enterprises
- Liaison with the Venture Capital investment community
- Increased market presence by leveraging social media promotions, community leaders and classic media reporters
- Recruited, developed and increased partner ecosystem in Russia, Middle East and Israel
- Over achieved yearly regional overall quota for 2 consecutive years

CIO at ClickSoftware LTD

September 2003 - April 2010 (6 years 7 months)

- Initiated, developed and executed SAAS strategy designed to penetrate mid-market segments. This was achieved with no risk to traditional line of business by repackaging the company's traditional (client/server) software products for SAAS based delivery without code modifications or capital investments
- Lead global IT teams based in the US, UK, Germany, Australia, Israel and India
- Leader of the corporate SOX compliance program, corporate security and DRP strategy which was executed in the recovery operations (DR) of the main corporate office of the company resulting essential systems back online in an alternative location within 12 hours with no data loss
- Mentored team members to grow as leaders and professionals and as service professionals
- Responsibility of worldwide Information systems Strategy, hiring and procurement software, hardware and investments in data center facilities

IT Systems Team Lead at Creo

September 2001 - 2003 (1 year 4 months)

- Lead multi-cultural team of 25 engineers supporting 1200 users across the US and Canada
- Achieved more than \$800,000 in operational cost savings via multiple consolidation efforts
- Responsible for IT Corp yearly budget of 5MM which includes Oracle based ERP systems

IT Systems Administrator at Scitex

April 1997 - June 2001 (4 years 2 months)

- Launched a new version of the corporate web site (Scitex.com), introducing web technologies such as a search engine, web forms and improved web-oriented graphic design Project resulted in 300% growth in unique site visits within the first year
- Implemented web analytics tools and provided management with monthly usage reports
- Lead migration efforts of various IT systems from proprietary VAX and AIX UNIX to HP UX and Microsoft Windows based systems

Education

The Hebrew University

MBA, Integrative Management, 2007 - 2009

University of Derby

BA, Business Administration, 2005 - 2007

University of Massachusetts Lowell

Dan Feld

Growing Google's Developer Ecosystems



Contact Dan on LinkedIn